Pablo Bordas Garcia

Software Engineer

Calle Pius XI 17 2 46017 Valencia (Valencia) (+34) 618 123 222 bordastrabajo@gmail.com



SKILLS

Experience in software development in the following languages: Java, C #, Apex and Visual Basic, both in Backend and Frontend

Experience in analysis, project management and direct contact with the client.

I have recently been involved in the analysis and development of multiple integrations between Salesforce and external systems, as well as in international projects, mostly with everis headquarters in London.

Amateur developer at Unity. Own projects published, example: Haunted Race

EXPERIENCE

Biobam Bioinformatics S.L., Valencia - Engineer

October 2021 - February 2022

- Development in Java, Dockers and GitHub Actions.
- Administration and development in Salesforce (Integrations, web portals, REST and SOAP services, maintenance, test)
- Environment completely in English

Omega CRM, Remote- Engineer

December 2020 - August 2021

- Administration and development in Salesforce (Integrations, web portals, REST and SOAP services, maintenance, test)
- Analysis of evolutionary and change demands in Salesforce.
- Environment completely in English

Everis, Valencia - Engineer

October 2017 - July 2020

- Administration and development in Salesforce (Integrations, web portals, REST and SOAP services, maintenance, test)
- Analysis of evolutionary and change demands in Salesforce.

Everis, Valencia - Practice employee

July 2017 - October 2017

 Software developments in the Enterprise & Cloud Solutions section of Salesforce.

FGV - Ferrocarrils de la Generalitat Valenciana, Valencia - Software

programmer - Practice

December 2016 - April 2017

 Development of the new web page for incident control at railway facilities using: C #, SQL and HTML5

EDUCATION

Universitat Politècnica de València (UPV), Valencia - Bachelor of

Engineering, Computer Engineering

July 2013 - April 2019

In the final thesis, Integration between Salesforce and an external system, one of the integrations between systems implemented in Salesforce in Everis is analyzed.

LANGUAGES

Inglés B2 accredited by the Universitat Politècnica de València (UPV)

Catalán - Native